Guide to the Isidore Sydney Falk Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Professional Activities, 1919-1979; Series II; 44 linear feet (107 boxes)
  - Social Security Administration, Bureau of Research and Statistics
    - Research and Planning Files
      - General papers
        - Memoranda and related material, Advisory Council on Social Security, Senate Committee on Finance, 1947-1948 (Box 69, Folder 692)
        - Presidential message re: social security and health insurance, 1947-1951 (Box 69, Folder 693)
        - Notes re: health and welfare and education expenditures for 1960 (S.J. Mushkin), 1948 February (Box 69, Folder 694)
        - Memorandum re: financing of a national health program (L.E. Epstein), 1948 April 22 (Box 69, Folder 695)
        - "A Practical Program of Health Insurance" (I.S.F.), 2 drafts, for The Nation's Health -- A Ten Year Program, 1948 May, September (Box 69, Folder 696)
        - Memorandum, "Coverage under the Federal Old-Age and Survivors Insurance Program", 1948 October 1 (Box 69, Folder 697)
        - Financial reports of Blue Shield plans, 1948 (Box 69, Folder 698)
        - Memoranda re: U.N.E.S.C.O. medical benefit plan (I.S.F.), 1948 (Box 69, Folder 699)
        - Memoranda and notes re: joint F.S.A. committee on health insurance, 1948-1949 (Box 69, Folder 700)
        - Memoranda (J. Fisher, I.C. Merriam) and print material re: economic status of the aged, 1948-1949, 1952 (Box 69, Folder 701)
        - Memoranda and correspondence re: American Medical Association, 1949 January-May (Box 69, Folder 702)
        - Memorandum, "Some Criteria for Evaluating Proposals for 'Contracting Out' under the State Disability Insurance", 1949 February 1 (Box 69, Folder 703)
        - Memorandum re: policy position on "staging" (I.S.F.), 1949 February 7 (Box 69, Folder 704)
        - Estimates of expenditures under national health insurance, 1949 May (Box 69, Folder 705)
        - Memoranda re: health insurance allotments to states (A.W. Fifer, A.W. Willcox), 1949 June (Box 69, Folder 706)
        - Memorandum re: workmen's compensation (I.S.F., B.S. Sanders), 1949 November 4 (Box 69, Folder 707)
        - "Summary of Discussion of Union Management Welfare Plans and Their Relationship to Social Security" (W.J. Cohen), 1949 November 10 (Box 69, Folder 708)
        - Memoranda and draft, "A Statutory Formula for Allotment of Health Insurance Funds to the States" (I.S.F.), 1949 (Box 69, Folder 709)
        - Memoranda re: "Some Partial Approaches to Health Insurance for Mr. Hearst" (I.S.F. to O.R. Ewing), 1949 (Box 69, Folder 710)
        - Correspondence and related material re: Brookings Institution, Availability of Medical Service in the United States, 1949-1950 (Box 69, Folder 711)
        - Drafts (I.S.F.) and reference material for speech and article written for James E. Murray, 1949-1950 (Box 69, Folder 712)
        - Memoranda and report, "Monetary Appraisal of Present Commercial Insurance Protection Against Costs of Illness and Injury" (I.S.F., B.S. Sanders), 1949-1950 (Box 69, Folder 713)
        - Memoranda and related material re: Catholic Hospital Associations' voluntary health insurance proposal, 1949-1950, 1952 (Box 70, Folder 714)
        - Working papers re: estimate of expenditures for a national health insurance program, 1949-1952 (Box 70, Folder 715)
        - Memoranda and notes re: Brookings Institution, "The Cost and Financing of Social Security", 1950 February-June (Box 70, Folder 716)
        - Memoranda and reference material re: Blue Cross (A.W. Brewster to A.J. Altmeyer "for Denver debate"), 1950 March-April (Box 70, Folder 717)
        - Memoranda and reference material re: Blue Cross (A.W. Brewster to A.J. Altmeyer "for Denver debate"), 1950 May-September (Box 70, Folder 718)
        - Draft report, "Discussion of the Deductible Principle", 1950 June 19 (Box 70, Folder 719)
        - "Report No. 3 on Disability Planning -- Final Objective: Basic Issues on Program Procedures and Organization", 1950 July 31 (Box 70, Folder 720)
        - Memoranda re: 1952 budget, 1950 December (Box 70, Folder 721)
        - Memoranda re: workmen's compensation premiums (I.S.F., B.S. Sanders), 1950 (Box 70, Folder 722)
        - Memoranda re: O.A.S.I. premium costs, 1950, 1953 (Box 70, Folder 723)
        - Memoranda re: new treasury regulations on integration of private retirement plans and O.A.S.I. (R.J. Myers, W. Van Eenan), 1951 June-July (Box 70, Folder 724)
        - Memoranda and text, Vatican letter re: social medicine, 1951 August (Box 70, Folder 725)
        - Notes re: Blue Cross and O.A.S.I. hospitalization, 1951 October 12 (Box 70, Folder 726)
        - Memoranda re: 1.2 conversion factor used by insurance companies,(B.S. Sanders), 1951 (Box 70, Folder 727)
        - Memoranda (I.S.F.) and print material re: federal-state intergovernmental relationship, 1951 (Box 70, Folder 728)
        - Notes re: prepayment plans in California and Washington (I.S.F.), 1951 (Box 70, Folder 729)
        - Correspondence, report and related material re: social welfare expenditure in the United States, 1951-1953 (Box 70, Folder 730)
        - Memoranda, reports and related material re: wage and salary stabilization policies in employee benefits plans (I.S.F., W.J. Cohen, V.F. Gegan, J. Zisman), 1951-1953 (Box 70, Folder 731)
        - Notes and revisions for O. Ewing's "Report to the President on the Nation's Health", 1952 June (Box 70, Folder 732)
        - Mimeographed draft, "Social Security in the United States", 1952 June (Box 70, Folder 733)
        - Correspondence re: R.R. and W.G. Campbell, "Compulsory Health Insurance: The Economic Issues," Quarterly Journal of Economics, 1952-1953 (Box 70, Folder 734)
        - Reprints and drafts of response (I.S.F.) re: R.R. and W.G. Campbell, "Compulsory Health Insurance: The Economic Issues," Quarterly Journal of Economics, 1952-1953 (Box 70, Folder 735)
        - Memoranda re: labor force and dependents (J. Fisher), 1952 Sep, 1953 June (Box 71, Folder 736)
        - Notes re: "Are We All Destined to be Paupers?" Readers Digest (W.J. Cohen), 1952 November (Box 71, Folder 738)
        - Memorandum, "Some Selected Areas and Items in Social Security, Health and Related Fields of Social Welfare" (I.S.F.), 1952 December 14 (Box 71, Folder 739)
        - Memorandum re: income tax ruling 4107 (taxability of self-insured plan benefits), 1953 January 23 (Box 71, Folder 740)
        - Memorandum, "Proposals for Maturing the O.A.S.I. System", 1953 February 3 (Box 71, Folder 741)
        - Memorandum and reference material re: "Will You be Cheated by Social Security After Paying the Bill?" Look (R.J. Myers), 1953 April 24 (Box 71, Folder 742)
        - Notes re: "Some current problems and issues in Social Security", 1953 May 22 (Box 71, Folder 743)
        - Tables re: commercial insurance experience, 1953 June 10 (Box 71, Folder 744)
        - Memoranda and reprint re: F.J.L. Blasingame and F.G. Dickinson, "A Physician and an Economist Look At Old-Age and Survivors Insurance," Journal of the American Medical Association, 1953 November (Box 71, Folder 745)
        - Hospitalization and Insurance Among Aged Persons (I.S.F., A.W. Brewster) and memoranda, 1953 (Box 71, Folder 746)
        - Report and related material re: public assistance (W.J. Cohen), 1953 (Box 71, Folder 747)
        - Summary re: economics of medical care (I.S.F.), undated (Box 71, Folder 748)
      - Conferences
        - Transcript of proceedings, notes, and agenda for meetings with group hospitalization representatives, 1942 Jan, September (Box 71, Folder 749)
        - Transcript of proceedings and summary, Conference on Nursing Service in a Comprehensive Health Program, 1944 November 3-1945 May 24 (Box 71, Folder 750)
        - Correspondence and summary, Conference on Dental Service in a Comprehensive Health Program, 1944 November-1945 March (Box 71, Folder 751)
        - Transcript of proceedings, Conference on Dental Service in a Comprehensive Health Program, 1945 January 22-23 (Box 72, Folder 752)
      - Double-decker old age benefits, 1939-1942, 1952
        - Memoranda and reports (E.L. Dulles and staff), 1939 (Box 72, Folder 753)
        - Memoranda and reports (I.S.F., E.L. Dulles and staff), 1939-1942 (Box 72, Folder 754)
        - Memorandum re: cost effect (E.A. Rasor), 1953 August 6 (Box 72, Folder 755)
        - "Interim Report of Working Group on Double-Decker and Related Plans" and memoranda, 1953 August 19-20 (Box 72, Folder 756)
      - International Labor Office
        - Correspondence, 1935-1949 (Box 72, Folder 757)
        - "Provisional Record of the Social Security Consultation on Income Maintenance and Medical Care" (an-notated), 1943 July 9-12 (Box 72, Folder 758)
        - Plan of discussion and related materials re: Social Security consultation on medical care, 1943 July (Box 72, Folder 759)
        - Reports, notes and correspondence, Special Committee on Seafarer's Insurance (I.S.F.), 1945 June-September (Box 73, Folder 760)
        - Memorandum re: policy position (I.C. Merriam), 1952 July 11 (Box 73, Folder 761)
      - Permanent and total disability insurance
        - "Benefits for disabled persons and survivors, and supplemental allowances for dependents. A discussion of some possible revisions of Title II of the Social Security Act" (I.S.F.), 1937 November 5 (Box 73, Folder 762)
        - "Memoranda on extension of the Federal Old Age Insurance System to cover permanent total disability", 1938 December 9 (Box 73, Folder 763)
        - Bills and report re: S. 3924, Wagner Bill (Permanent Disability Insurance Act), 1939-1940 (Box 73, Folder 764)
        - Memoranda re: disability cost estimates, 1939-1941, 1943 (Box 73, Folder 765)
        - Memoranda re: S. 3924, Wagner Bill (Permanent Disability Insurance Act), 1940 March (Box 73, Folder 766)
        - Memoranda re: S. 3924, 1940 April 5-19, 1940 April 24-May 15 (Box 73, Folder 767-769)
        - Report and memorandum re: "The Wagner Bill and a critical review of its provisions", 1940 May (Box 73, Folder 770)
        - Correspondence and memoranda re: comments by consultants, 1940 May-July (Box 73, Folder 771)
        - Memoranda re: specifications and proposals, 1940, 1941 January-April 15 (Box 73, Folder 772-773)
        - Memoranda re: proposed plan, 1941 March-June (Box 73, Folder 774)
        - Memoranda re: specifications and proposals, 1941 April 17-May (Box 73, Folder 775)
        - Memoranda and summary of recommendations re: specifications and proposals, 1941 June-1942 January (Box 73, Folder 776)
        - Notes and memoranda re: proposed plan, 1941 July (Box 73, Folder 777)
        - Memoranda re: combined disability insurance system, 1941 August-October (Box 74, Folder 778)
        - Reports and memoranda re: proposed plan, 1941 August-September (Box 74, Folder 779)
        - Report re: proposed plan, 1941 September 25 (Box 74, Folder 780)
        - Notes and memoranda re: proposed plan, 1941 October-December (Box 74, Folder 781)
        - Memoranda re: Combined Disability Insurance System, 1941 November-December (Box 74, Folder 782)
        - Memoranda re: relation to workmen's compensation, 1941 (Box 74, Folder 783)
        - "Report on Permanent Total Disability Insurance" (B.O.A.S.I.), Circa 1941 (Box 74, Folder 784)
        - Social Security publications, 1941-1942 (Box 74, Folder 785)
        - Memoranda re: Combined Disability Insurance System, 1942 January-February 19, 1942 February 23-December (Box 74, Folder 786-787)
        - Memoranda re: civilian war injury proposal, 1942 (Box 74, Folder 788)
        - Reports and memoranda re: proposed plan, 1942 (Box 74, Folder 789)
        - Legislative bills, 1943 (Box 74, Folder 790)
        - Social Security publications, 1943-1945 (Box 74, Folder 791)
        - Draft, "Disability as a Cause of Economic Insecurity and the Need for Disability Insurance" (I.S.F.), 1943-1946 (Box 74, Folder 792)
        - Miscellaneous reference material, 1944-1950, undated (Box 74, Folder 793)
        - Legislative bills, 1945 (Box 74, Folder 794)
        - Report (B.B. Kendrick), 1945 (Box 74, Folder 795)
        - Memoranda and pamphlet re: number of disability cases, 1945-1949 (Box 74, Folder 796)
        - Report (B.S. Sanders), 1946 May (Box 74, Folder 797)
        - Memoranda and report, "Specifications for Extended Disability Insurance" (I.S.F., B.S. Sanders), 1947 January April (Box 74, Folder 798)
        - Statement, "The Meaning of Social Security" A.J. Altmeyer), 1947 December 4 (Box 74, Folder 799)
        - Legislative bills, 1947 (Box 74, Folder 800)
        - Memoranda (G.St.J.Perrott), 1947 (Box 74, Folder 801)
        - Memoranda for the Advisory Council on Social Security, 1948 January (Box 74, Folder 802)
        - Legislative bills, 1948 February-March (Box 74, Folder 803)
        - Memoranda for the Advisory Council on Social Security, 1948 February-June (Box 75, Folder 804)
        - Memoranda, proposals and reports, for the Advisory Council on Social Security, 1948 February-May (Box 75, Folder 805)
        - Legislative bills, 1948 April (Box 75, Folder 806)
        - Report from the Advisory Council on Social Security, 1948 May (Box 75, Folder 807)
        - Legislative bills, 1948 June (Box 75, Folder 808)
        - Memoranda and report (R.J. Myers, D.F. McCamman), 1948 (Box 75, Folder 809)
        - Miscellaneous print material, 1948-1952 (Box 75, Folder 810)
        - Memoranda and reports re: program administration, 1949 February (Box 75, Folder 811)
        - Bill and related material re: H.R. 6000 (Social Security Act Amendments of 1949), 1949 April-August 1 (Box 75, Folder 812)
        - Bill and related material re: H.R. 6000, 1949 May 17 (Box 75, Folder 813)
        - Memoranda and reports re: program administration, 1949 June-September (Box 75, Folder 814)
        - Bill and related material re: H.R. 6000, 1949 August 2-15 (Box 75, Folder 815)
        - Memoranda and reports re: H. R. 6000 (R.M. Ball, O.C. Pogge), 1949 October-1950 January (Box 75, Folder 816)
        - Legislative bills, 1949 (Box 75, Folder 817)
        - Memoranda (I.S.F., B.S. Sanders), 1949 (Box 76, Folder 818)
        - Statement (O.C. Pogge) and report re: H. R. 2893, 1949-1950 (Box 76, Folder 819)
        - Memoranda and reports re: H. R. 6000 (R.M. Ball, O. C. Pogge), 1950 (Box 76, Folder 820)
        - Memoranda and report (W. Van Eenam, R.J. Myers, B.S Sanders), 1950-1952 (Box 76, Folder 821)
        - Legislative bills, 1951-1953 (Box 76, Folder 822)
      - Temporary disability insurance
        - Notebook, reports and related working material, 1937 (Box 76, Folder 823)
        - Notebook, working papers re: legislation for federal-state temporary disability-unemployment compensation program, 1937-1940 (Box 76, Folder 824)
        - Supplements re: definitions, costs, certifications and rates, 1937-1940 (Box 76, Folder 825)
        - Memoranda (I.S.F. and staff), 1941-1943 (Box 77, Folder 826)
        - Miscellaneous print material, 1942-1952, undated (Box 77, Folder 827)
        - Notes and memoranda re: Rhode Island Unemployment Compensation Board (I.S.F., J.J. Corson, A. Patt), 1943 January-February (Box 77, Folder 828)
        - Memoranda (I.S.F., A.J. Altmeyer), 1943-1946 (Box 77, Folder 829)
        - "Survey of Accident and Health Insurance," bulletins 1-6 (R.H. Blanchard) and related material, 1945 November-December (Box 77, Folder 830)
        - Memoranda and related material re: S. 1734 (National Unemployment and Temporary Disability Act), 1947 (Box 77, Folder 831)
        - Text for panel discussion, "Health, Welfare and Retirement Plans in Relation to the Social Security Program" (A.J. Altmeyer), 1947 January (Box 77, Folder 832)
        - Statement re: proposed legislation for cash sickness benefits (W.J. Cohen, B.S. Sanders), 1947 February 12 (Box 77, Folder 833)
        - Memoranda (M.C. Klem), 1947-1948 (Box 77, Folder 834)
        - Social Security Administration report and publications, 1947-1949 (Box 77, Folder 835)
        - Memoranda and reports re: savings in assistance costs, 1948 (Box 77, Folder 836)
        - Memoranda and reports re: railroad temporary disability insurance, 1948-1950 (Box 77, Folder 837)
        - Report re: railroad temporary disability insurance program, 1949 August 8 (Box 77, Folder 838)
        - Speech text re: collective-bargaining welfare plans (I.S.F.), 1949 November (Box 77, Folder 839)
        - Memoranda and related material re: private health insurance, 1949-1950 (Box 77, Folder 840)
        - Memoranda and reports re: H. R. 2893, Doughton bill (I.S.F.), 1949-1950 (Box 77, Folder 841)
        - Notes and pamphlet re: New York, 1949-1950 (Box 77, Folder 842)
        - Memoranda and pamphlet re: California temporary disability insurance, 1949-1952 (Box 77, Folder 843)
        - Correspondence (I.S.F., W.J. Cohen), 1951 (Box 77, Folder 844)
        - "Comparison of Temporary Disability Insurance Laws, April 1952", 1952 April (Box 77, Folder 845)
        - "The Use of Sickness Insurance Claims as a Means of Gaining Knowledge of Morbidity", undated (Box 78, Folder 846)
        - United Auto Workers
          - Correspondence and reports, 1945-1949 (Box 78, Folder 847)
          - "The Problem of Establishing a Medical Care Program for Members of the U.A.W.-C.I.O. in Detroit" (F. Goldmann), Circa 1946 (Box 78, Folder 848)
          - Agreements and programs, 1949-ca. 1950 (Box 78, Folder 849)
        - United Steelworkers of America
          - "Report of Joint Fact Finding Commission on Insurance", 1948 March 1 (Box 78, Folder 852)
          - Miscellaneous print material, Circa 1949 (Box 78, Folder 853)
          - Report and statements presented before the Steel Industry Board, Circa 1949 (Box 78, Folder 854)
          - Insurance agreements between union and companies and related print material, 1949-1950 (Box 78, Folder 855)
          - Correspondence and notes (I.S.F.), 1950 April-August (Box 78, Folder 856)
      - Unified social insurance
        - Working papers and plans for comprehensive federal social insurance, Circa 1939 (Box 78, Folder 857)
        - Working papers, 1939-1943 (Box 79, Folder 858)
        - Working papers re: "Social Security for Everyone," part one, 1943 (Box 79, Folder 859)
        - Working papers re: "Social Security for Everyone," part two, 1943 (Box 79, Folder 860)
        - Working papers re: "Social Security for Everyone," part three, 1943 (Box 79, Folder 861)
      - United Mine Workers Health and Welfare Program (Krug-Lewis agreement)
        - Drafts of agreement and telephone notes, 1946 May (Box 79, Folder 862)
        - Correspondence and drafts of "A Preliminary Study of the Welfare and Retirement Fund Created by the Bituminous Mine Agreement, May 29, 1946", 1946 June-August (Box 79, Folder 863)
        - Correspondence, notes and questionnaires, 1946 September (Box 79, Folder 864)
        - Correspondence, 1946 October-December (Box 79, Folder 865)
        - Telephone notes (I.S.F.), correspondence, and statement, "The New Labor Contract in the Bituminous Coal Industry", 1947 February-August (Box 80, Folder 866)
        - Correspondence, 1947 September-Dec, 1948 Feb, 1973 January (Box 80, Folder 867)
        - "Notes on Bituminous Coal Pension Plan" (M.W. Latimer) with notes by I.S.F., 1948, undated (Box 80, Folder 868)
        - Chronology of the United Mine Workers of America Welfare and Retirement Fund, 1949 June (Box 80, Folder 869)
      - Voluntary insurance
        - Cash Benefits Under Voluntary Disability Insurance in the United States (Elizabeth L. Otey), 1940 June (Box 80, Folder 870)
        - Draft memoranda and notes for United Steelworkers of America, 1946-1949 (Box 80, Folder 871)
        - Working papers (I.S.F., A.W. Brewster) and report, 1948-1949 (Box 80, Folder 872)
        - Social Security Bulletin reprints, 1948-1955 (Box 80, Folder 873)
        - Working papers (I.S.F., A.W. Brewster) and report, 1949 (Box 80, Folder 874-876)
        - Notes and tables re: voluntary health insurance estimates, 1950 August 2 (Box 80, Folder 877)
        - Working papers (I.S.F., A.W. Brewster) and report, 1950 October-Dec, 1950 January-September (Box 80, Folder 878-879)
        - Report (A.W. Brewster), 1951 January 18 (Box 80, Folder 880)
        - Working papers (I.S.F., A.W. Brewster) and report, Circa 1952 (Box 80, Folder 881)
        - Notebook re: information on voluntary health insurance in the United States, 1953 and earlier (A.W. Brewster), 1953 December (Box 80, Folder 882)
    - Publications
      - General
        - Report to the President of the Committee on Economic Security, 1935 January 15 (Box 81, Folder 883)
        - Constitutionality of the Social Security Act; Opinions of the Supreme Court of the United States, 1937 May 26 (Box 81, Folder 884)
        - Proceedings and other publications of the National Health Conference, 1938 Jul 18-20, 1938-1939 (Box 81, Folder 885)
        - Compilation of the Social Security Laws, Circa 1939, 1947 (Box 81, Folder 886)
        - Regulation No. 1 and Regulation No. 3, 1940-1941 (Box 81, Folder 887)
        - Old Age and Survivors Insurance, 1948 (Box 81, Folder 888)
        - Recommendations for Social Security Legislation, 1949 (Box 81, Folder 889)
        - Congressional committee reports, 1951-1952, 1955 (Box 81, Folder 890)
        - A Report to the Secretary of Health, Education, and Welfare on Extension of Old-Age and Survivors Insurance to Additional Groups of Current Workers, 1953 (Box 81, Folder 891)
        - Social Security After 18 Years, 1954 (Box 81, Folder 892)
        - Compilation of the Social Security Laws, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 893)
      - Board of Trustees of the Federal Old-Age and Survivors Insurance Trust Fund
        - Annual reports, 1942-1948 (Box 81, Folder 894)
        - Annual reports, 1949-1954 (Box 82, Folder 895)
      - Bureau of Research and Statistics
        - Social Security Bulletin: reprints, 1939-1940, 1946 (Box 82, Folder 896)
        - Bureau Memoranda, Circa 1940-1952 (Box 82, Folder 897)
        - Fact sheets, 1944-1946, 1949-1951 (Box 82, Folder 898)
        - Social Security Bulletin: memoranda, 1951-1953 (Box 82, Folder 899)
        - Social Security Bulletin: notes (I.S.F.), draft and reprint of Ida C. Merriam article, 1953 (Box 82, Folder 900)
        - Social Security Sources in Federal Records, 1935-1950 (Abe Bortz), 1969 (Box 82, Folder 901)
      - Miscellany: pamphlets and leaflets, 1940-1948, undated (Box 82, Folder 902)
    - Miscellaneous Papers
      - Articles by A.J. Altmeyer, Circa 1919, 1942, 1946, 1954 (Box 83, Folder 903)
      - Speech text, "Health Service and the Public, an Examination of Conflicting Social Philosophies" (Maurice William), 1943 December 13 (Box 83, Folder 904)
      - Texts of speeches by Social Security staff, 1938, 1943, 1948, 1953-1955 (Box 83, Folder 905)
      - Excerpts from public opinion polls re: health insurance, Circa 1947 (Box 83, Folder 906)
      - Administration Health Program, a Training Kit for Leaders, Democratic National Committee, 1950 June (Box 83, Folder 907)
      - Five Lectures on Social Security (E.E. Witte), 1951 (Box 83, Folder 908)
      - Magazine article written for H.H. Lehman (I.S.F.), 3 drafts, 1951-1952 (Box 83, Folder 909)
      - Correspondence and notes re: Robert F. Wagner's career, 1952 May (Box 83, Folder 910)
      - Social Security Amendments of 1955: bill and related print material, 1954-1955 (Box 83, Folder 911)
      - Background materials for Medical Advisory Committee Conference on the Disability Freeze, 1954-1955 (Box 83, Folder 912)
      - Speech text and news release re: Social Security history (M.B. Folsom, E.E. Witte), 1955 August 15 (Box 83, Folder 913)
      - Memoranda, statements and report, 1955-1956 (Box 83, Folder 914)